I was born and raised in Ohio.
When I was three years old, my father died in a semi accident.
He was hit by a semi truck coming home from work one night.
After that, there was a lot of hardship and a lot of struggle.
There were days we were not sure if we were going to eat or not.
In fourth grade, teachers told my mum that I was too hyper and I needed to be on medication.
I was then put on medication.
As the years went on, I was still depressed, even though I was on medication.
I started drinking and taking drugs.
And then, fast forward, after college - few months after I had graduated -
I tried to take my life by taking a bottle and a half of pills.
One night, I was just feeling so low, broken; my girlfriend at the time had just broken up with me.
I had just lost my job and was feeling so low.
I just felt like there was no reason for me to be alive.
So, I took a bottle and a half of pills and drank a bunch of alcohol.
Then, I drove to my friend's house.
I don't even remember driving there.
It was a miracle that I even made it to my friend's house.
In the middle of the night, I woke up and remembered that I had taken those pills.
I tried to stand up and go to the bathroom to throw up the pills
but my legs were numb from the effects of the medication.
I couldn't stand up, so I had to crawl to the bathroom.
When I got to the bathroom, I tried to throw up the pills.
That is the last thing I remember because I blacked out and went into a seizure.
The next thing I know is that I woke up in an emergency room.
I literally thought it was a dream.
After I got out of the hospital, I was still drinking and feeling depressed.
Then, I met an evangelist from The SCOAN.
She gave me a bottle of the New Morning Water by Prophet T.B. Joshua.
When I got home, I began to minister it to myself,
began to apply it to myself everyday, believing God for healing and deliverance.
And I got that healing.
A couple of months later, I was able to throw out all the pills.
It's been almost six years now that I have taken medication.
Now, I feel free and good.
I used to be depressed and suicidal.
Now, I work full time for the Emmanuel TV USA team and we work with all kinds of kids
that grew up in hardship just like I did.
We feed the homeless, help the elderly, and do all kinds of great things.
I am just so thankful and grateful that God used Prophet T.B. Joshua
to bring the New Morning Water into my life and heal and deliver me.
If God can do it for me, He can do it for you.
This INCREDIBLE TESTIMONY Will Touch Your Heart!!!
TT: Mel Flowers 02/08/2018
RV ROBERT BEGIER 11/08/2018